{
  "category1": {
    "topic": "Highs and Lows",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Ocarina of Time, Twilight Princess Sales",
      "answer": "OoT, 14MM vs 10MM"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "McDonalds, Starbucks Locations",
      "answer": "Starbucks, 15.2k vs 13.5k "
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Asia, North America GDP",
      "answer": "Asia, 39.8 vs 34 trillion USD"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Africa, South America GDP",
      "answer": "South America, 4.2 vs 2.8 trillion USD"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "M*A*S*H, My Little Pony Friendship is Magic Episode Count",
      "answer": "MASH, 256 vs 230"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "U15 boy, open female powerlifting total",
      "answer": "Female, 1620.4 vs 1592.8 lbs"
    }
  },
  "category2": {
    "topic": "Legal Leg Ends",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "How many professional games has Faker played?",
      "answer": "1,434 (87 champions)"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Doublelift's highest winrate champion, excluding pick rates below 10.",
      "answer": "Xayah, 30-10"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Does Sneaky have more instagram posts, or professional games as Lucian?",
      "answer": "Instagram, 75 vs 68"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Name a player with a pentakill in more than one role.",
      "answer": "Caps, Optimus, BeBe, SofM, Zz1tai"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Who has played more professional games, Faker or the current 100T roster?",
      "answer": "100T (387 more games)"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Which champion has the highest pentakill rate?",
      "answer": "Smolder, 4.88 games/penta"
    }
  },
  "category3": {
    "topic": "Topic 3",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Name one Super Monkey Ball monkey",
      "answer": "AiAi, Baby, GonGon, MeeMee"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "DOTA 2 dominates esport prizewinnings. For the top earning players, which game shows up first after DOTA 2?",
      "answer": "Fortnite, Bugha, #22 alltime earner"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Of the top 50 all time esport prize winning earners, how many play DOTA 2?",
      "answer": "45"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "How much prize money has been won between all Farming Simulator (any edition) tournaments?",
      "answer": "871,281.29 from 40 events"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "How thicc are the contiguous stats, measured SSE-NNW?",
      "answer": "2,848 miles"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Within the first 15 games of LEC Winter 2025, name one of three 100% pick/ban champions.",
      "answer": "Viktor, Kalista, Skarner"
    }
  },
  "category4": {
    "topic": "Um, Actually",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Halo installations are overseen by Forerunner monitors, usually identified with a series of numbers followed by a name. 343 Guilty Spark is the monitor assigned to Installation 04, though before becoming a monitor 343 Guilty Spark was the Florian known as Riser from Erde-Tyrene. ",
      "answer": "343 Guilty Spark was built from Chakas, a human."
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Titus Groan is the heir of Lord Sepulchrave, the seventy-sixth Earl of Groan, in the castle Gormenghast. Titus has three sisters, Violet, and the twins Cora and Clarice. Finally, the mother Countess Gertrude can be seen roaming the grounds with her birds and cats.",
      "answer": "The first sister is named Fuchsia, not Violet."
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "August Kitko, titular character, is an excellent saxophonist who finds himself merged with one of the Vanguard Mechas from space. Using his musical ability he is able to communicate with the Mechas and act as a conduit in an effort to save the Earth.",
      "answer": "August Kitko plays piano"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  },
  "category5": {
    "topic": "Topic 5",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Who is the consensus GOAT of Starcraft Broodwar?",
      "answer": "Flash"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  },
  "category6": {
    "topic": "Topic 6",
    "question1": {
      "double": true,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Question 1",
      "answer": "Answer 1"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  }
}
